WindWalker is a GPT-powered web app builder for small businesses.
A user describes the business they want to run.
For example, a digital bookstore with member login, cart, checkout,
purchase history, downloads, and an operator dashboard.
WindWalker turns that request into a workflow pattern, generates a responsive
web app preview, and lets the user refine it through conversation.
When the app is ready, it is deployed to Cloudflare Pages as a live URL.
In this demo, the deployed bookstore supports mock member login,
product browsing, cart interaction, and test checkout.
The same workflow can be adapted for bookings, quotes, customer intake,
support, and other small-business operations.
We used GPT-5.6 for final iteration and validation, with OpenAI Codex
supporting implementation, testing, and submission evidence.
GPT can generate an app.
WindWalker helps small-business owners launch, operate, fix, and continuously
improve that app with workflow patterns and lightweight human support.